Hello everyone, welcome to our year-end special live broadcast. Today is our year-end party.
First of all, I would like to introduce myself to everyone. I am Yana from CLOUD, and I have been providing live broadcast information to everyone on WeChat, Weibo, and Douyin, and answering everyone's questions and communicating with everyone.
I am very happy to meet you as a live broadcast today.
In addition to me, I would like to introduce the teachers around me.
Hello everyone, I am Lili. I am a great friend of mine.
Hello, I am Lili, and I have been providing live broadcast information for the last ten years.
Hello everyone, I am Tina, thank you for being here today.
Hello everyone, welcome to CLOUD, and I am the teacher who participates in this event.
How do you express your feelings to each other?
First of all, my name is Tina.
My beauty and beauty of talents are all thuiss.
I thank you, my beautiful family, the channelério.
Hello everyone, I am لив.
I am Lili's daughter, I moving from Lyon.
Hello, I am Tina.
Good boy.
Okay, then we...
She's going to sit on the small chair.
Okay, she's going to sit on the small chair.
Oh, oh, oh.
She's excited.
Then our
year-end event will start today.
First, let me introduce to you
the three processes of our special live stream.
The first part
is the reaction of our teachers
to your works.
I believe you all saw that
at the beginning of December,
we released an announcement
to collect your final works.
The first part is
the reaction and evaluation
of our teachers to your works.
Before this,
C didn't show their works to them.
So now these teachers
don't know what their works are like.
Wow, I'm so excited.
I heard you received a lot of works, right?
Yes.
The second part
is the review of
all 28
CLO
live streams this year.
The third part
is the Q&A
in advance.
We will answer
your questions
about CLO software,
teachers' life,
and personal questions.
Without further ado,
let's get into the first part.
Let's get into the first part
of our teachers' reaction.
Let's first look at
the first work.
It's from
ID Wei.
I'm sorry,
I can't pronounce your name.
it should be Lee You-sing.
Maybe that's how you pronounce it.
Let's let our teachers
read it.
Wow,
it's so dreamy.
It reminds me of
the girl's dress.
I think the bottom
is pretty
loose.
It feels like
they used
a different color.
It feels like
they used a different color.
It's very well done.
It's pretty much the same.
So the way they
processed it
will make it good.
Let's take a look at the comments.
If you think this is a good work
you can give it a 1.
But let's look at the details.
We can give some advice
about the details.
For example, the top
of her shirt
feels thick.
I don't know if it's
the fabric.
If you look at this dress, there shouldn't be such a big fold in the hemline.
It's a bit deep, isn't it?
Yes, it's a bit like made of space cotton.
But I don't think it's that deep.
Of course, it depends on the design of the dress.
If you are the author, you can share with us in the comments how you made this dress.
Now let's move on to the second piece.
Wow!
This...
The details are well done.
Wow, this button.
This style reminds me of...
It reminds me of the female detective from the detective series.
It's a bit like a school uniform.
It's pretty good looking.
The details of the dress, including the thickness of the collar, are well done.
The thickness of the dress is also well done.
The overall details are well done.
Yes, if you look at this big detail picture,
you can see the sense of encouragement from the branches.
It's the feeling of fur.
Yes.
Teachers, remember the feelings you see in every piece of work.
In the end, we will choose the best piece of work in your mind.
We will give the best piece of work to the author,
and give them a mysterious gift.
After watching the reaction video,
we will reveal it to you.
Now let's move on to the next piece of work.
The next piece of work is from...
This fan's name is Tatika.
She gave us a message.
Not just a message,
the message from the email is also very touching.
The first day I saw the message,
I cried.
It's true.
I will share it with you later.
Let's take a look at her work.
Wow, this is so modern.
It looks like the cover of a magazine.
Wow, this hat.
And it has a mirror.
Wow, I saw this in the live broadcast of Ms. Yan's live broadcast.
Yes, yes.
So cool.
It's very active.
It's a live broadcast with special effects.
It's a combination of a scene,
and the overall color scheme is black and white.
Yes, and then...
It's more harmonious.
Yes.
But if you look closely,
maybe because it's a bit far away,
if you look closely,
you can feel the texture of the clothes.
It's a little weak.
Yes, it's not very clear.
Maybe you have to look at the details to make a judgment.
Yes.
And this suit...
Maybe it's the model's posture.
This posture...
The arm is a little stiff.
I feel like I can give her...
If I give her a more natural posture,
it will be better.
Yes, yes.
Okay.
If you think it looks good,
I will give it a shot.
Okay.
Next up,
the next work is from
a user whose ID is YuEr.
Wow.
This is the work that I sent to you.
The red one.
This is from the last live broadcast.
Yes, yes.
It's another live broadcast of Mr. Yan.
Yes.
What a pity.
Mr. Yan can't come to the scene today.
Where is Mr. Yan going?
Mr. Yan is going to the 5th Banlang this year.
So it's a pity that he didn't come to the scene today.
Again, it's...
But you can clearly see that the author has watched our previous live stream with Caithong.
And you can see that she studied very hard.
Yes.
Basically, the whole details are done.
Her wrinkle treatment is not bad.
From the details, her wrinkles are basically all out.
In other words, the quality has been improved.
I can give you a small suggestion.
You can add some more details to the neckline.
Add some more details to make the outfit look more realistic.
Yes.
But look at her hat.
There are a lot of three-dimensional pearls on her belt.
Yes.
It looks pretty good.
We have to remember the look of this work.
But I feel like this hat...
We are not done yet.
I think we are done.
I feel like I just saw it.
I feel like the thickness of this hat can be made thicker.
It's a little bit thin.
But the upper part...
The bottom two layers of the hat are not too thin.
Yes.
Overall, it's pretty good.
She has made the red smoke-like effect on the back of her shirt.
It's pretty good.
It's a little bit like a product picture.
Then, let's...
Teachers, please remember this artist.
Let's move on to the next one.
The next one is from...
It's from the company of Kairin.
It's a work of Kairin Wang.
Let's take a look.
This is a bag.
Wow.
The craftsmanship of the bag is so good.
Let's take a look at the details.
Actually, from the details, the production of this bag is quite good.
Yes.
It's made of cotton all over.
So the volume of the version is quite large.
The production of the bag by another company is actually very detailed.
So it takes a lot of patience.
Yes.
The zipper and the buckle structure.
And the back.
She also made a...
It's a structure that covers the zipper.
Yes.
Maybe the pattern is too flowery.
Some of them can't be seen.
But there is a structure over there.
I don't know if she made the structure inside.
Anyway, it's made like this.
It's pretty good.
Let me give you some more advice.
I feel that...
Well...
The zipper on the two layers of the bag is a bit stiff.
You can adjust the zipper according to the weight of the bag.
It will be more natural overall.
Overall, it's pretty good.
It's not easy to make a bag like this.
Wow.
One of the fans said,
The anchor, Typhoon Wenjian.
Hahaha.
Thank you, this user.
Thank you for saying that we are Typhoon Wenjian.
Hahaha.
Let's move on to the next work.
I believe you all remember this bag very well.
The next user is Chen Fuzheng.
Her Bilibili ID is zhenan.
Let's take a look at her work.
Wow.
She is the daughter of a gentleman.
Oh, yes.
That's how I reacted.
You can take a look.
Oh.
She made this kind of hairpin.
What is it?
There are two small balls on it.
Hmm.
Is this a couple's outfit?
I want to ask you.
Hahaha.
And I want to ask,
Why did you put two of these?
Is it a couple's outfit?
Is the light below a little different?
Or is it a three-dimensional effect?
I feel that the left side is different.
Yes.
The left side may not have a calligraphy.
The right side uses a calligraphy.
So the whole part of the calligraphy,
The three-dimensional effect will be stronger.
The three-dimensional effect.
Anyway, the quality of the calligraphy is still very high.
Yes.
There is a comment saying that
I feel that the two textures are different.
Yes.
The one on the right is obviously
She used a calligraphy to make an outtouch.
A real outtouch.
The ball on the top
It's also using the material of the hair to dye it.
The effect is still very realistic.
Including the mark on the back.
The details are done very well.
It's a pity that there is only one work.
If this author can provide a full body match,
I feel that it will be very good.
This outfit is a full body match.
It must be very good.
Yes.
Let's look at the next work.
It's a work from Zhuang Zeyan.
Wow.
She did so much.
And every one of them.
I want to give her a 666.
Wow.
I really like the model in it.
I like the one on the left most.
I also like it.
It's elegant.
I also like the one on the left.
Yes.
It's very Dior-like.
The overall look on the left is quite high.
Including the suit.
And there is a belt on it.
There are also some metal details on the belt.
Yes.
The one in the middle is also good.
The one in the middle is high street style.
I found a model myself.
This model is quite Asian.
Yes, quite Asian.
Wow.
They all say that the one on the left looks good.
Yes.
The one on the left looks good.
And the one on the right.
It looks like the one on the front of your shoes.
Yes.
Wow.
And this one on the right.
There are also a piece of metal detail on the right side,
Yes.
It's made of needles.
It's nice.
The details are fine.
It also has a good texture, including the thickness.
The right side of the button is also...
You can also clearly see the two layers of the neckline.
Also, this picture is actually a little...
It's a little far away.
I don't know if you can see it when I zoom in.
Some of the feathers in the needlework.
Anyway, from this distance, it looks a little bit like this.
The feeling of feathers.
The texture is very well handled.
Because he is actually very concerned about the details.
I just saw that there were comments from fans.
When can we get to the question and answer section?
Fans can...
This little friend can wait a little bit.
This time...
Xiaoxi didn't tell you just now.
This time's draft work
I'm really going to blow up my mailbox.
This time we received...
We received a draft work of 30 artists.
And then...
The number of works...
I can't count it.
Maybe it's going to be a hundred.
And then these are selected by us.
But...
We still have 20...
The draft work is selected.
So we will come slowly.
But don't worry about the fans.
Then let's look at the next work.
It's from this one.
Kinsley's classmate.
Then he is a student from Hong Kong.
Let's take a look at his work.
Wow.
This Molly, your...
This is the live broadcast I watched that day.
Wow, the window on the left is Molly's.
Then the two sets in the middle should have watched my live broadcast.
Yes, yes, yes.
Right, right, right.
Where did you find it?
I learned it by heart.
Yes.
Because what he does is very complete.
Look at the hat, the bag.
The jeans are also designed.
It just feels like the clothes on the right side of Kinsley's are a little unnatural.
Maybe it's because of the physical properties.
Yes.
The state of the hanging is a little...
But the one on the left is pretty good.
And you can see that he actually learns very well in every class.
Yes.
Basically all of them.
Wow, we are so happy to have taught this homework.
This is really the model of teaching homework.
Yes.
You can take a look.
If you like the live broadcast.
Okay, then we are going to move on to the next work.
Then this work...
This author's ID is very deep.
It's called silence is the best choice.
Let's take a look at his work.
Is it as cool as his ID?
Wow.
These two...
Wow, the style is so different.
It's so different.
Wow, it's really two works made by one author.
The lace on the left feels pretty good.
There's also a screen in the back.
But if you look closely,
the clearness of the lace on the left seems to be not high.
Right?
Maybe it's because of the dyeing.
I think it's because of the lace.
Especially the bottom part.
And the lace on the bottom part
looks like a shiny piece of paper.
Does it look like it?
A little bit.
If it's a shiny piece of paper,
you can consider adding some hair stickers
or calligraphy.
Make it look three-dimensional.
Then you can add another...
What is it called?
You can add another sticker on the surface.
Or you can use our new 6.0 function,
which allows you to create a metallic texture.
This way,
the shine will be closer
to the bling bling effect.
Don't get too excited.
Lie down.
Thank you.
Okay, let's move on.
The style on the right feels pretty good.
The model on the right is also very dynamic.
Yes.
The fashion is also pretty good.
She's wearing a bling bling jacket.
Is it a bling bling shirt?
Yes.
It looks like it's open.
It's probably lace bling.
Yes.
This style is a bit like
that of the MD next door.
The snow-coated teacher next door is saying
why am I being cued at home.
The whole design on the right feels pretty good.
Yes.
The model is really dynamic.
You can't say you're a model, you're just wearing clothes!
The point is the clothes, right?
The whole set of colors and designs are pretty good
I'm talking too much, I'm not talking anymore
Let's look at the next work
Next is Xiao Hong's work
Wait for your big butt
This little butt
It's okay
Next is Xiao Hong's work
Shopping
Let's take a look
Wow
The contrast between these two colors is pretty good
But if you look at the left side, you can see the details of the album
The details of the album, like the lights and the piglets
Little doggie, don't steal our microphone
There's another one
It's her work
Oh
This one is pretty good
This scene, I think she made it herself
I think so
I think she made it herself
The big scene outside is probably made by other people
But this one should be made by herself
Let's eat some snacks, don't mind us
We haven't eaten dinner yet
Dingqiu came over
It's quite good
The shirts on the top
The shirt is quite realistic
It's her style
Dingqiu you can't eat it, I'll feed you
Oh, she even made the cross-dressing
I don't know if she made it a bit messy on purpose
It's quite good
I like the yellow sleeves
I like it too
I like the blue skirt more
It's different from yours
Do you think yellow is better or blue is better?
You can comment below
Yellow is better or blue is better?
I saw someone asking
How does the pattern look like?
I think it's from the sweater
The pattern of the sweater is very simple
You have a piece of fabric
Or a sweater
You scan it
After you scan it
You can apply the pattern
You can also make a pattern
With the pattern
Next
The next one is from
G
Her name is Yama Lu
Let's see what kind of clothes she can wear
She has a bag
She's a little C
Zhou Juelun also said
She's very pretty
This is a very casual dress
She made
Two shoulder straps
Yes
And she also carried one
I think that bag
Attracted my attention
I think her
The pattern of the pants is very good
The pattern of the pants
Yes
I think it's inspired by a torture
This kind of water-based BN
I feel something like she's gonna do
An explosion
The details of the pants are pretty good
Yes, you can see the waist
The very three-dimensional
The feeling of the pressure
Good
Let's look at the author's
Another work
Oh, there's more
I like her earrings
It's so cool
Look, it's a bit like Chewing.
Take a closer look.
One hook, one hook. Oh, it's a C!
Are you trying to make a commercial for us?
Really!
She also made a necklace.
Yes, there's a necklace, a bracelet, and a small bag.
This artist should have used a lot of other software.
Look at the shoes.
Yes, she poured it in from other places.
The whole thing is very complete.
How did she make this? I want to know.
She made a torn effect.
It should be a transparent sticker.
Yes, a transparent sticker to make this effect.
You also know it's a transparent sticker.
Even the dogs know, but I don't.
The sleeves are also made of wool.
But I don't think the texture of the top is very clear.
Maybe the color is too dark.
Yes, the color is too dark.
Okay, let's move on to the next work.
It's a work by Xin Lin.
Let's take a look.
I really like her second one.
It's a bit like a dress.
And the first one, Fei Fei, also put on makeup.
Because the texture of her work is very good.
Including the shine of her pearls.
Every pearl has the shine of a pearl.
Yes.
Someone in the chat said that the author has appeared.
The author has appeared?
Tie Guo Jian You Yu said that I actually have mine.
Which one is hers?
Which one is yours?
Are these three clothes Tie Guo?
Are you Xin Lin?
Yes, it's Tie Guo Jian You Yu.
Oh, I just found out.
I'm sorry.
I should have seen the eyes.
We have eyes.
We can see the water.
Yes.
Oh, she said that we have taught her.
Thank you.
Her right side, the glass beads feel pretty good.
Yes.
Including below, you see, it's a bit of a snowy material.
And then there's some transparent snow in the middle.
Yes, she's stepped on all the materials.
Made a...
So she...
And the snow on her right waist, she deliberately pulled it.
Yes.
Anyway, these details, I feel that the texture of the fabric and the physical properties of the fabric are very well controlled.
The processing of the pattern is also very good.
Seeing such a student, we are really very pleased.
Yes, she is also very touched. She said she was recognized.
Yes, it's pretty good.
It's really well done.
Yes.
You can give yourself a wave of clothes.
666.
I really like the middle of the clothes on the left.
I also like this one.
The floating in the middle should be blown up by the wind controller.
Yes, I think the middle of the clothes is a little bit...
Maybe it's because we enlarged the picture.
Or maybe it's because of the TV here.
It's not very clear.
I can see it clearly on the computer.
It's pretty good.
The one on the left is pretty good.
The fabric is also good.
The design is also good.
The two on the left and the right should be the same...
It's almost the same board, but it's made of two different styles.
I want to ask this student.
Did you design the wedding dress?
Yes, it's pretty good.
You can answer.
She has been in our chats.
She said thank you.
Wow, wow, wow.
Is there anyone else who wants to apply now?
I can't apply now.
This is her graduation design.
Wow.
Cool.
OK.
Thank you, Xinling.
She's also an ID for Iron Fist.
Now let's move on to the next work.
She's still a student.
Oh, you're still a student.
Cool.
What does that word mean?
What word?
The air suddenly...
What?
The back waves are retreating.
The back waves of Changjiang are retreating.
The front waves are dying.
Don't say that.
Let's move on to the next work.
It's from Zhu Peishan.
Wow.
This is my favorite work.
Wow, the quality of the draft is so good.
I can't even look at it.
This pink is amazing.
I think the colors are very good.
I don't know if this student is in the live stream or not.
I don't think so.
If she is, she will respond to us.
Is it because our live stream time is early today?
Some people don't know.
So many people don't know.
But it doesn't matter.
There are three minutes left. It's 8 o'clock.
Oh, mine is here.
There are three minutes left.
I believe there will be more students coming in.
I like it very much.
It's on the left again.
This one on the left.
I like this one.
She is wearing three pieces of clothes.
Four pieces.
She is wearing three pieces on the upper layer.
Maybe I didn't say it clearly.
And there is a necklace.
I think the jeans on the right side are very real.
It's the kind of water-washed texture.
Yes, including the inside.
Look at the sides.
Yes, yes.
They are made by Fengfeng.
The details are good.
There are belts and bags.
I think everyone is better at controlling the details.
The details of live streaming are eternal gods.
The details are good.
Of course, we have to rely on the students' knowledge.
She is very serious about learning.
She said this is her senior's work.
Awesome!
I think the style of these two works is very similar.
They will be doing another event.
It's a sweater. It should be green.
The sweater's fur feels good too.
Yes.
There's a new member.
The pink one with the two blue sleeves, the knot,
it takes time to do. It's done well.
I really like this one. If it's on sale, I want to buy it right now.
Okay, let's thank Zhu Peishan.
She's also a student of Hot Pot.
I saw Dong-ge entered the live stream.
Dong-ge, hello!
Hello, Dong-ge.
I think there will be her later. I heard she also applied.
Dong-ge, there will be your work later.
Please wait a bit.
Now it's our 14th work.
Okay.
It's Wan Ting's work.
Wow, this is amazing.
This is like an advertisement.
Yes.
With a factory-style background.
The pose is very natural.
There are several poses.
Wow.
I'm already shocked.
Even the dogs are watching.
Look at her details.
Yes.
Her texture is also very good.
You can see the texture on the left side.
Yes, this yellow one should be made with the same shine as the leather.
I think the yellow one should be the texture of cotton and wool.
It's very bright.
Most fans have sharp eyes.
They can tell that the socks are of different colors.
Yes.
I think the overall look is very good.
It reminds me of the socks.
When I look at the socks, it seems that I can sit tighter.
I think her pose is very natural.
Look at this model.
It should be Mara.
I think it's not easy for her to be so natural.
Mara will cry if she is soft.
Don't dislike my Mara so much.
Yes.
But if you pick the bone in the egg, I think you can adjust the setting of the fur.
You can make it more dense.
Yes.
This fur looks a little thin at the moment.
It's not like this expensive fur.
If it's thin, it can enhance its value.
Make it more dense.
So she made a gradient fur.
Look, it's black inside.
Yes.
It's black inside.
So you must have watched the fur live stream carefully.
Yes.
The fur hair live stream.
Plus the complicated hair dress live stream of Nico last week.
You must have learned a lot.
Yes.
Let's look at the next work.
The next work is from Chen Ming.
Chen Ming, are you in the live stream?
Yes.
Someone asked how to put your hands.
How to put your hands into your pockets?
Why would you put your hands in the pockets?
You just scoop your pockets with aigan.
And then adjust the hand.
Okay.
Then let's take a look at Chen Ming's work.
Oh.
This is another fashion highlight.
Yes.
I think it's already been developed online.
I think this is a very well- estavam cocoa freelancer.
It's very professional.
It's free.
From the color combination to the outfit, to the bag, to the pose, to the background, the whole color combination is very good.
Yes, I think everyone has mastered this multi-piece outfit very well.
And it has a detail. Look at the blue one on the left.
Because she made such a pose with her hands, she deliberately made the pants higher and lower.
Yes, this detail makes the whole outfit look more casual.
It's more artistic.
But I think it's a little bit lacking in the background.
I think the yellow background is a little bit too strong to match the blue one.
She probably wants to make a contrasting color.
To make the blue outfit stand out more.
But I think the left one...
Because the blue one can be drawn in detail on some of the details of the craftsmanship.
For example, like the corner of the foot of the pants.
Usually there is a curving craftsmanship.
But now it looks like...
I can't see too clearly on this picture.
I don't seem to see it.
It's something like this on the craftsmanship.
I think the purple background on the right.
If you add a Vogue on it, it can be used as a magazine cover.
The right one looks very natural.
Yes.
This model looks very similar to the one in the front.
Is it the one in the front?
The small model.
Is it the one in the front with the earrings?
Yes, but I don't see the face on the top.
But the style is similar.
It's a small, young, white model.
This model looks good.
But her clothes look good too.
Oh, Dingqiu.
Don't scare the dog.
She saw a strange man outside.
She saw a strange man.
Okay, okay, okay.
Dingqiu, let's go.
Sit, sit, sit.
Oh, the comments are all scared.
Sorry.
Dingqiu, sit down.
Sit down, sit down, Dingqiu.
Dingqiu, let's go.
Oh, the comments answered that she is the model of Daz.
Oh, that's good.
Do you still want to eat?
If you think this work is very good,
you can call me.
Encourage me.
I like this set of works.
The comments are all saying that she is the next model.
The next model.
Okay, let's stop arguing.
Okay, let's move on to the next work.
Oh, Dongge.
Dongge, your work is here.
Dongge, did you see it?
Dongge, your work is yours.
Wow.
ワ
This is…
This is a wedding dress.
I know.
I've been looking for the structure for a long time.
It's a drum.
It's blowing out the wind.
It's blowing up the bottom of the drum.
I've been looking for a long time.
Dongge's work is very celebrated.
This set of color arrangement.
The key is that she gave this dress a light that is not in line with the light source that we predicted, right?
This light is yellow, like the color of the sunset.
This is very high-end.
This kind of cross-sectional feeling is very good.
You can even see the texture on the cross-sectional.
I want to ask what material she used on this model.
What material is this?
It should be plastic.
The height is very low.
It becomes a very smooth plastic.
And the bottom is stepped on a metal board.
It's pretty good, pretty good.
It's a simple and elegant dress.
I feel like she added some craftsmanship to the sleeves and neckline.
Some craftsmanship details can be added to make it look thicker.
It's a little thin now.
But overall, it's pretty good.
We're all talking about giving her some food.
Come, come, come.
Dingqiu, haven't you eaten dinner?
I just ate a lot of chicken breast.
Dongge, we're done introducing your work.
We're going to move on to the next work.
Dongge, I don't know if you saw it.
Dongge didn't even show up.
Dongge just showed up for a moment.
Now she's gone.
She's gone.
The next one.
Dongge, you can only watch the replay of our reply.
The next work is from He Lei.
You can take a look.
Wow.
Her heavy workmanship is very Dior.
Miss Dior.
Yes, yes.
Heavy workmanship.
She made a lot of three-dimensional flowers.
I thought this would be quite a group work.
The details of the flower are very good.
The craftsmanship details on the skirt can be added a little more.
Dongge is back.
But I think the fold on her chin is a little bit off
The part where she's touching the lotus leaf
Oh, a little bit
But the wood ears on the top are pretty good
Wow, everyone is talking a lot about this flower
Yeah, the flowers are changing
Everyone is curious
There's also that one in the yellow dress
Wow, you guys are so meticulous, I didn't even notice
There's a vest in here
And outside there's a school uniform
Wow, everyone is talking about this
And look at that skirt
There's also a skirt that's made of sand
Oh, everyone wants to know how Hua Hua did it
It's Xu Boyuan
Maybe next year we'll have a live stream about dresses
We'll see if we can arrange it for everyone
Everyone wants to learn how to make flowers
Come on
Let's look at the comments
Let's see how many people want to learn
If there are a lot of people, can we arrange it as soon as possible?
We need to arrange it in the back stage
Then let's
Next
If you want to learn something, you can say it in the comments
The next work is from a writer called Stone
Wow
It's a very new work
Wow, this one
The overall completeness of this one is also very high
And I think it's very similar to the previous group's completeness
But I think this one is pretty good
It has a very strong sense of texture
Yes
I didn't notice this one in the middle
I just looked closely and found that it's a hollow one
Yes
But a little bit, I think, if you say
Because this one should be the kind of hollow feeling that you want to make a pinwheel
So I think your jacket gives an advantage
You can make the material of the fabric a little softer
It may be a little bit more similar
The sleeves are a little bit harder
Because it's the kind of
The red one in the middle
Because it's a hollow pinwheel
It should be a little bit softer
If it's a hollow pinwheel
Its stretchability should be more
It should be said that its strength and strength of the pinwheel
Should be relatively small
It's a stretchable kind of pinwheel fabric
So it should have more of a wrinkle
Yes
But we just picked the bones in the egg
Yes, yes, yes
Pick the bones in the egg
Give some advice
But the overall feeling is still good
The red one in the middle
This set of colors
He also gave him a bag
Yes, actually, these two are also
You see, it's the same
A change of two materials
Yes, the same
Red
Then use different fabrics
Yes
But the feeling is very different
Yes, yes, yes
All look good
I like it
Actually, I like the color combination on the far right
I also like
This is very normal
You can wear it directly on the street
Yes, yes, yes
What are you thinking about wearing it?
I'm thinking about this belt part
Yes
It seems that you made a double layer
The knot
Take a closer look
Look at the red one
The one below
Yes
Is it like a double layer?
You mean the belt, right?
Yes
And then this
Because this is a very light leather
I feel that I can make it a little harder
Because now it looks like this
This kind of leather is still a little soft
But I feel that this kind of leather belt
It should be generally harder
Of course, it's also an egg to pick bones
But in general, it's still pretty good
Not bad
This is really good
Yes
We all ignore those two little ones
In fact, the little one did a good job
The little one did a good job
Yes
But the blue skirt on the left
It's a little unnatural when it comes out
But the two big pictures in the middle are still very good
Wow
There is a comment that says
After watching the big god, I have no confidence to learn
Wow, don't have no confidence to learn
Many of our fans have been following our lessons all the way through this year
Yes
Take your time
Don't worry
Then let's move on to the next work
The teacher has to remember him
Remember
Then the next
Oh
The next one is a video work
Is it a video?
Yes
Then we still have
Let me take a look
We still have two works left
First of all, it is a video work from a classmate from Lin Xiangyun
We can take a look
Lolita
Oh my god
invest
10 rings
10 coins
Let's do it
Wow, they're all saying new
I can't say that word anymore
We can still say 666
So cute
The details are good
Wow, it's good
Can we do it on the recording?
Sure
Stop
This is so cute
Yes, there are a lot of details
And you can see there are a lot of layers in the showroom
Everyone can pay attention to the title
This work has a theme
If you can't afford it, you can make your own
It's okay
After you finished the choreography
You have all the versions
You can make your own
It's good
Wow
I'm thinking
Our students
Are really good
Yes
There are a lot of voices
Then we
If you say you have to pick up the bones in the eggs
I realized I'm so bad
I always pick up the bones in the eggs
This sentence has appeared many times
I just feel that the clothes are moving
The red waist belt
The removed This is great
It's empty
We can leave a little
Ok
You can pay attention to its shoulder strap
Really very clean
It's a little shaky
Maybe
Yes
At this time, it means that the waist belt
Not the waist belt
The shoulder strap isn't fine
And the gill gills
She may be big
When you shake it, you can't open it, so you shake it with it.
At this time, it is recommended that you make a fine-tuning of your shoulder strap.
Make the fine-tuning a little bigger.
Or you can use a fake needle to set it on your inner layer of clothes.
Or you can set it directly on your model.
Set a few more like this.
This can prevent your shoulder strap from shaking too much.
Someone asked me a question.
If you have a skirt, how do you wear it?
That's right.
Oh, the pants are still strawberry.
Yes, this little detail is too girly.
I didn't even see it.
Look again.
Is it really strawberry?
Yes, there is a strawberry on it.
Okay.
We are going to move on to the next work.
I saw someone in the comments.
Is there any expensive company clothes for teaching?
I haven't been able to buy it.
All of our Bilibili teaching videos are free.
Every time our teacher does a live broadcast, it is free.
What else do you have to spend money to buy?
Our Bilibili platform has free teaching videos.
There are Chinese dubbing and subtitles.
Now they are all uploaded.
Then there is our teaching recording and live broadcast.
Then there is our official website.
There is also a teaching manual.
You can search for it and learn from it.
Then our accessories are in the WeChat public account.
Yes.
Then we are going to move on to the next work.
How do you hold a skirt?
You have to make a skirt.
That is, if you say the skirt of other Maya software.
That kind of thing.
Well, it doesn't seem to be.
That is, you can do it as a solid hard film.
Hold your fabric inside and simulate it.
Then you can also use it in Clue.
Use Clue's fabric to make a skirt.
To play a supporting role.
Then the way to make a skirt.
You refer to the actual one.
The real skirt.
Its one.
The principle of function.
That is, what kind of shape it is.
What principle does it use to support your skirt?
When you make this in 3D.
It is also based on that kind of logic.
To build a structure.
Okay.
Then we can enter.
That is today's last reaction work.
It is from.
I'm sorry.
I don't know if it's right to say this.
It should be.
I read it as Lou Yang Studio.
It should be read like this.
He is also on our Bilibili.
Published Clue works.
A very frequent one.
A very cool one.
A cool person.
So is this an Asian drama?
It should be.
Can it be considered Asian?
I don't know if you are in the live broadcast room.
We are going to see your work next.
First of all, it is also a video.
Yes, he has two works today.
I'm looking forward to it.
First of all, the first one.
What will the Asian one look like?
Asian.
Asian's first one.
Wow.
Is this a big one?
6666.
Oh, this is a little bit hard.
He's here.
The author is here.
The god is here.
He's here.
It looks like an Asian drama.
A little hard.
commen.
Oh.
There's a name.
It's called spirit.
distinctive.
Enjoy!
Isn't it?
Really?
It's really good.
I feel bummed.
Then let's take a look at his.
I'm looking forward to it
Yes, I'm looking forward to it
Looking at the details of the outfit
There are some unusual things that can be added
This can make the outfit look more like a formal one
Because like the one I'm wearing right now
Danger
A dog
The dog seems to be very familiar
The place where the outfit ends
For example, the corner of the feet
Or the cut
It's all too clean
It's just cut
There are no scratches
Or anything
Add some details
The details of the outfit
The depth of the outfit
Of course, this is just
The bones in the egg
The time is about to end
Wow wow wow
This is so pretty
The hair is so curly
I think
The boys would like this kind of outfit
But there is no leg
Right
If you look at the photo
This is probably
This feels like it's high-height
It runs to the side of the leg
This is the waist
Wow this one
Wow
I didn't think of it
Wow, I feel it
This one
I don't know why
I didn't think of it
My hair is so messy
I don't know why
But this feels more stylish
Very stylish
Really
It's really nice
I'm reading the comments
There is a comment
It's a little old
A little young
Although a little older
Everyone is old
This trend
I think it's
Not really
The year is all about
Wow
It's the last thing
The girls are all changed
There are seven places
I will go to all the places
I go to all the places
When I want to come here
This is the last time
It's like
You just need to work hard
Thank you, thank you.
Wow, thank you.
Thank you to the student from Lou Yang Studio for the work.
Wow, this is really amazing.
Yes.
Well, our reaction is over here.
All of our teachers are now going to choose the first place in your mind for all of your previous works.
So, first of all, for all of our reactions this time,
we will be giving away a souvenir around our clothes.
You can take a look.
Our custom-made 2021 calendar.
And our custom-made bag.
Can you see it?
It might be a bit delayed.
It's okay, we'll just move it around.
Move it around.
Let's move it around.
All of the students who participated in the reaction,
all of the students who participated in the selection of the works,
will be given a souvenir,
a calendar and a bag.
Next, our teachers will choose the first place in their minds.
And for the first place in their minds,
they will also be given a custom-made,
can you see it?
A custom-made humidifier.
So, let's move it around and take a look.
No one has been chosen.
There's a comment saying,
can we have someone who hasn't been chosen?
If you haven't been chosen,
you can have someone who will be chosen for the next draft.
Of course, you can have someone.
Okay, then we...
You can also scroll through the comments
to see which work you like the most.
If you can't remember the numbers,
you can describe the work.
You can do that.
So, our teachers will also start choosing.
Now, let's take a look at each work.
You can scroll through the comments.
Okay.
This is the first work.
This is the second work.
This is the third work.
This is the fourth work.
This is the fifth work.
This is the sixth work.
This is the seventh work.
This is the eighth work.
This is the ninth work.
This is the tenth work.
This is the eleventh work.
This is the twelfth work.
This is the thirteenth work.
This is the fourteenth work.
15th
16th
17th
18th
19th and 20th are
two videos, one is Lolita's skirt
and the last one is the fashion show
So do you have
the first place in your heart?
Don't choose 20th
I think everyone's previous works are all great
So do you have the first place in your heart?
Wow, wow, wow, there's something different
18th, 15th, 12th
Everyone has their own choices
Okay, have you all made up your mind?
It's so hard to choose
It looks like you haven't
If you've made up your mind, you can say it first
Okay, roll down and take a look
Yes, some people say that the techniques are all okay
It's just that the fashion style is different
It's true, so it's hard to choose
Yes, so it's hard to choose
It depends on everyone
It depends on everyone's taste in the comments
Wow, I'm really touched
Our trainees, everyone's techniques are all good
After learning for a year, after learning live,
the techniques are all so good
It's really amazing
Yes
If the teachers can't remember the numbers,
they can also describe which work it is
Have you all made up your mind?
I'm almost done
Okay, Lydia has made up her mind
What about Xina?
I want to choose
Chen Lie and
Jiao Zuoye
It's the most perfect Jiao Zuoye team
I want to choose that team
Oh, the one from Hong Kong
Yes, because I think she
watched our live stream very seriously
So I think it's really good
This one is from Hong Kong
Kingsley
I don't know if I read it correctly
Lydia chose your work
as the number one in her mind
At that time,
in your gift bag,
there will be one more special souvenir
plus a poem
What about Tina?
Look down
Lin Xiaoding
She said, thank you, it's me
Congratulations
Let me see, number 8
Number 8
Everyone is saying number 8
Look down
Xinyu is the one who followed the live stream
without any foundation
Wow, we're going to get a ticket
Wow, you can get a ticket
in the live stream
Let me look up
Tatika said it's number 17
Why don't you give your own work a ticket?
Wow, what a kind Tatika
I want to look at number 12
Let's look at number 12
Our teacher is really
very careful
I also like number 12
I really want to give it to her
Why? Because I think she's really good
at controlling her fabric
including the materials
I really want to give it to her
Look down
She got a ticket
Is there any
has Ms. Molly decided on this?
No, not yet
I wrote a bunch
Xinyu said it's okay
Oh, it's fine
As long as she agrees
If I remember correctly
Xinyu
in our last month's
6 PM conference
Is it...
The audience also got our prize. If I'm not mistaken, I just suddenly thought of it.
Yes, thumbs up.
That's really good. Maybe it's still you this time.
I think we have to give this work of No. 20 a vote.
No. 20 is already silent.
Yes, we definitely have to give it a vote. The strength is here.
No. 20.
Ah, Tieguodunyu got the mouse.
What did you choose, Molly?
I quite like No. 12.
You like No. 12? Then I'll choose No. 20.
No. 12.
Yes, I really like the one on the left.
Right? I also like this one.
But if I have it, I'll definitely get it.
Yes, our No. 12 will make food.
Actually, I also like No. 18.
No. 18.
Oh, I also like it.
What should I do?
Why don't you also pick one?
Me too? Can I? Then I'll also pick one.
Then I'll also pick one. Little C will also pick one. I'll take a look.
Wow, our Little C picked one.
You guys are giving me a hard time.
I picked No. 20.
Oh, you already picked No. 20, right?
Yes, I picked No. 20.
No. 20, the strength is there, so I'll definitely pick No. 20.
Yes, yes, yes.
Then let's congratulate No. 20, Luoyang Studio.
Then your prize will also add a humidifier to our surroundings.
So, did you think about it, Ms. Molly?
No. 12.
It came to my mind at the same time.
Okay.
So, Ms. Molly, in the end...
No. 13.
Then congratulations to the iron pan and squid student.
Then you can also get one of our humidifiers.
Then if I choose...
They are all awesome.
They are all awesome. Oh my god.
Who should I pick?
Okay, then I'll pick No. 18.
I really want that pink outfit
Lastly, congratulations to our No.18
No.18, Stone
You also won our extra gift of a humidifier
We are so touched
That's it for our reaction part
Now it's No.8, No.12, No.18, and No.20
No.8, right?
Yes
Okay
Okay, so this is the second part of our live stream
A full-year live stream review
I believe that after a year of teaching
You all have learned a lot about CLOUD
We saw that the previous works were not well-known
But we have learned a lot
After a year of learning
The teachers' hard work was not in vain
In the next part
Our designer, Ms. Molly
Will take everyone to review our live stream this year
Next, let's give a small round of applause to Ms. Molly
This year, due to the pandemic
Because of the pandemic, everyone is working from home
So we...
We have been working from home for a month in February
And we have planned to do a live stream
So in February, when we were working from home
We had this plan
We had the first live stream with Ms. Ivy
I hope you all have seen it
After the resumption
In March
We officially started an overall live stream of the basic teaching series
There are a total of seven chapters in the live stream
And then from the third chapter of making shirts
I have...
In each live stream
We added some small items
If you watch each live stream
You will see those small items
And then all the live stream materials
Can be obtained from our WeChat official account
And then in the same time as the basic teaching live stream
According to the requirements of the fans
We simultaneously started our Master Automobile
It should have started in June
We have done a total of 14 live streams of Master Automobile
In these 14 live streams
We have divided them into
Let's first look at the first one
It can be divided into
Make the costume look more real
And then there are a total of seven live streams
The first one is the毛发渲染全攻略
In this one
You can see the different毛发 settings
Different parameters and adjustments and applications
Like we just had a work
It's the fur in the complex piece of the down jacket
You can refer to it later
This is the毛发 of Ms. Ivy's live stream
And then the second one is
My live stream of渲染材质全攻略
In this live stream, we talk about
In the type of our hair dyeing material
In addition to the hair dyeing material
There is a setting for all other hair dyeing materials
Thank you, teacher
You're welcome
And then the third one is
There is our He Chuan Lu Zhou Jie Lun broadcasts
The module drawing topic
And then he talks about
Switching different modules
And then dyeing in the module drawing
Preserving
And then using the module drawing
To create a costume
And then the fourth one
It's a live stream of our teacher Lydia
A whole strategy of text processing
Yes, this class is still very helpful
In fact, in the previous one
We saw that in the homework we were taught
There is a sense of text in the individual homework
It doesn't look very strong
You can take a look at this class
In this class
He made a description of all three maps
And then next is a detail
It's a live stream of two detail expressions
The last one is about a piece of pig hair dyeing
And the eighth one is about bra and the eighth one is about a day
And then under the detail expression
It's what Tina said
It's a production of some detail parts
Of the twist, knot, and dress
Yes, in this live stream
Tina is in
In the twist, knot, and dress
These techniques
To give you an introduction
Then I saw in the homework you taught
There are some twists
And then there are some dresses
That's all in this episode
Yes, yes
And then there is one more
It's about a complex dress
A special topic
It talks about some
Pressure glue, three-dimensional tape
And some production of four-box
Cuff and hat
And the second part is
A production of the later stage of the costume
And one is the show-off strategy
It's also taught by Tina
In this show
It actually talks about
If you want to bring some accessories
To the show-off
In fact, there are some techniques
All of them are universal
So if you want to
Have an understanding of the show-off
This section is still very suitable
In fact, it also talks about
Very
There are a lot of very useful
This kind of little skill
And then the next one
Is a function introduction of the rendering page
It's from our designer
To do a live broadcast
There is also a
It talks about lighting, lens
And some settings for rendering properties
And then the third one is
A self-disciplined model of my streamer
And in this one
I see that
Today's teaching homework
There are a lot of people
Using DAS models
I think everyone should have
Seen this topic
In this one
I also talked about
How to change the skin
And then make a production of its movements
And then there are models of other software
And then there are
The fifth one is
Mr. Yan, who is doing half a wolf today
Such a cool special live broadcast
I saw that today
Someone should be
Referring to his live broadcast
I saw that there was a face-to-face talk, right?
Yes
And it feels like
There are a lot of people
Who are teaching homework
After listening to this class
Yes, there are a lot of people teaching homework
This class
Yes
Including some of the works
That have been submitted to us before
It's also based on
An inspiration from this class
To do some works
Yes
And then the next one
Is virtual clothing chain
It's also from me
And then today
I saw that
No. 8 works
Talk about
Using DAS models
Yes
And then talk about
Using virtual clothing
And then it's still very happy
Wow, the teachers may be 18 years old
Wow, thank you
Thank you
And then there's another one
On the other side
It's a sachet making special
It's also from us
He Changlu, Zhou Jielun
Today's little C
Oh, I think
The one who has a sachet today
Should have watched his live broadcast
Deity
Yes, Deity
Zhou Jielun sneered on the side
And then this
Is all of our live broadcasts this year
Don't forget to look forward to the live broadcast
Thank you
Hello
Deity
I didn't get to unmute you
I want to say hello
So
Do you know
Miss Ban
Miss
Hi
I think I've seen it before. There are instant noodles, pig's feet, durian, coconut milk, squid, and squid, right?
Yes.
Squid, squid.
Teacher, do you remember anything that is very old?
If you have any memorable moments during this year's live broadcast, you can post them in our chats.
Or you can post in the chats which teacher you like the most.
Although it might cause a fight between teachers, but it's okay, as long as you're happy.
Later, our singer-songwriter will give you a comment.
For the first effective answer, we will give you a souvenir.
Yes, we're going to draw a prize.
Yes, you can post it in the chats.
You can post your favorite teacher or the oldest lesson you remember in the chats.
As long as it's about our memories during this year's live broadcast.
Yes, as long as it's about our memories, you can draw a prize.
Someone just asked which teachers we have from left to right.
From left to right.
Let's introduce ourselves again.
Raise your hand.
I'm Lydia.
This is the live broadcast of Wenli.
It's 6pm.
It's a new feature live broadcast.
I'm here to introduce you.
I'm Tina.
I'm here to talk about the show and the details.
It's about the twist lesson.
I'm Yana.
I've never done a live broadcast for you.
But I've been serving you behind the scenes.
I've been on WeChat, Bilibili, Weibo, and Douyin.
I reply to your comments and answer your questions.
I'm Yana.
I'm Molly.
I've done 10 live broadcasts for you.
What you see on Bilibili is a video with Chinese dubbing and Chinese subtitles.
I did the dubbing.
And I did all the basic teaching live broadcasts.
Wow, this person said she remembers the festival the most.
I'm touched.
Then let me vote for Tina.
Wow, someone said I'm greedy.
I like it.
When I think of her expression, I want all of them.
Okay, let's do the live broadcasts.
We're going to draw the prizes.
Oh, I haven't told you yet.
What are the prizes for the live broadcasts?
The prizes for the live broadcasts are the extra prizes we gave to the reaction works.
Some of you just did it in the live broadcasts.
Can the live broadcast fans also get this prize?
It's our custom-made humidifier.
It's a humidifier.
This humidifier comes with a light and a small fan.
But why not?
Because I lost it.
But the ones I gave you all have it.
It's a new package.
You can take a look.
I don't know if you still remember that there's a shortcut key.
There are four shortcuts.
She drank your water.
Drink it.
Do you still remember that I was doing the dubbing?
There are four shortcuts.
Someone said I should ask my mom to press the shortcut key for me.
Wow, they're all saying that only children make choices.
How about adults?
Adults, dot dot dot.
Teacher Mo Ni.
She wrote Teacher Mo Ni.
Tang Yu, Xiao Du, Jia Feng.
Chen Li's class.
Oh, it's my class again.
Here.
Thank you.
She also wrote Wen Li's class.
Thank you for saying I was in the middle of a festival.
Are we voting?
No, no, no.
Teacher Mo Ni and teacher Wen Li's class.
Which teacher is teacher Wen Li?
Teacher Wen Li is our leader.
Teacher Mo Ni's memory game is that you guys are eye-catching memory games.
Later, everyone in the chat room will be eye-catching.
This is the first time I'm being eye-catchy.
I'm working overtime.
Special effects.
The chat room is in the chat.
We have a comment here.
It's from Yan.
It's a pity that he's working as a half-wolf.
He's working as a half-wolf right now.
He should be able to watch the live stream.
I don't know. Let's see his message.
Okay, we have a comment here.
I remember the time when Siyin ran out.
Yeah, I was working overtime.
I was working overtime.
I was watching the live stream.
Why did Siyin suddenly rush out and start laughing?
What's going on?
That taillight.
How did he make that light?
That taillight is really...
Oh, he's talking about Xunran.
Yeah, there's still a taillight.
He typed it wrong.
He's using his own accent.
Is it too late to hand over the homework now?
It's too late.
Next time. Next time.
What should we do next time?
Taillight.
Is half-wolf teacher handsome?
If half-wolf teacher wants to work with the live stream again, let him work with it.
Let's let you see how handsome he is.
Taillight.
How charming.
I remember that Taillight class was a remote closed class.
Right?
We did the live stream at Diantiu's house.
And I remember I was sitting in Diantiu's bedroom.
I remember I was sitting in Diantiu's bedroom.
The fan who wrote this,
his last name is 1531.
He said,
看猴几遍 感动 感动 错过等一年 声音记忆深刻 因为什么记忆深刻 好听呀
啊 亚娜老师 谢谢你 谢谢你 我今天第一天来你就谢谢我嘛
虽然那个台灯快要把我逼分 因为一直有人在问我灯是怎么做的 灯是怎么做的 我都说了灯照是用版片做的 灯里就做个球嘛
那我们差不多可以刷起来 嗯 差不多了 那个结论你可以往上滑一下 截屏了 然后在粉丝面前截一下给大家看一下
现在要开始抽奖咯 模特笑死了 笑死了
大家有弹幕的吗?
现在滚起来啊 开始抽奖了 开始抽奖了 稍等一下 可能有点延迟
你就往上 诶 Jeremy 你就往上一滑 然后截图
这么多嘛 刷起来了 刷起来了 刷起来了 刷起来了 刷起来了 截屏了 截屏了
三 三 等等等等等等 慢慢来 重新来 重新来
等等等等等等 慢慢来 重新来 重新来 重新来
预备 三 二 一 截屏
这是什么? 这是什么? 这是什么? 第一个有效答案
给我看一下 你给那个看一下 给摄像头看一下
哎呀 这个结论动作有点慢 大家理解一下
诶 怎么 怎么重新来呢?
看一下 看一下 结论平时写歌写多了 手比较 手比较抖
手比较抖 来看一下
可以呀
哦 不是很清晰 哦 不是很清晰
很清晰呀
不是 怎么念
哦 尾号什么什么的
结论你把这个对着 对着那里
对着那里说 尾号谁谁谁谁谁
的这一位
是
稍等一下有延迟
是这个呀 尾号呀
四零一四五九五这个呀
打结打结 打结打结
这个 第一个 第一个
第一个
诶 第一个
诶 这个结论真的手速实在是有点慢
你给大家看一下
看得见吗? 我们要不要切换到那个大屏幕啊?
嗯 可以可以可以可以
要不要切换一下大屏幕
切换到那个
给大家看一下啊
我们中奖的
点什么
结束
给大家看一下
稍等一下
结论的手速有点慢
看到了吗?
大家看到了吗?
对焦一下
哈哈哈
你好搞笑
你把手挡在你的手机屏幕后面
诶 对对对
挡在 再往下来一点吧你的手
可以可以可以
尾号是
尾号是1495
弹幕说了打结打结
这一位
那之后你要联系一下
弹幕有人说可恶不是我
哈哈哈
那你可以联系一下我们
哔哩哔哩的后台私信联系一下
我们的小CG
那也就是我
我会给你联系的
然后你只要把你的联系方式发给我们就可以了
好
是我吗
对就是你
请你记得联系一下我们的私信联系一下
哔哩哔哩
我们的官方号
告诉一下我们
告诉一下我们你的地址就可以了
那我们下一个
嗯
那接下来呢我们就要进入本次直播的第三个环节了
要回答大家的疑问
那在先前小C给大家的微信公众号呀
还有哔哩哔哩各个方面的预告里面呢
我们也发出了二维码来让大家进行扫描提问
这里我们挑选了一部分大家的问题
那么现在就要让我们老师进行回答吧
那么在老师给大家解答问题的时候
大家千万千万不要离开直播间哦
因为我们会在直播的
我们会在解答的过程中
随机进行提问
那么如果答对我们问题的小伙伴
也同样像刚刚一样能够截屏滚动
获得一个我们的加湿器的奖品
那我们先来解答一下大家的问题吧
第一个问题
如何在模特身上进行立裁
那可以给我一下鼠标吗
那这个问题的话
其实
可以借助我们软件里面的这几个工具
那首先的话第一个就是
我们的这个
叫做3D
画线的这个工具
是在虚拟模特身上画线的一个3D笔工具
那它可以在模特身上画线
然后呢在
3D线去提取一些3D版片
那就是
当然这个比较适合一些就是贴身的这种服装
可以直接提取版片出来
那其他的另外一些工具呢比如说我们的这个固定针
它可以把你的版片固定在模特身上
以及我们6.0以后呢
使用到的是这个
在模特身上去创建一些测量线
那然后可以使用这个
在这里有一个叫贴附到虚拟模特身上的这么一个功能
去把你的版片贴附到模特上
那这两组都是
固定3D版片到模特上的一个功术
用这两个工具辅助来固定你的3D版片
然后基于你3D服装的形态去调你2D中的一个版片的形态
然后基于你3D服装的形态去调你2D中的一个版片的一个形态
所以想要在3D里面做立裁
就是在CL fare里面做立裁
你得同时看3D的效果
3D effect and then make a real-time adjustment in 2D, of course, you can also use this tool
For example, your costume is finished and then you want to make a adjustment to the shape of the costume
You can also use this 3D pen tool on the clothes to draw lines on the clothes
Then you can also adjust the shape of the line on it and then make a cut or seam and so on
So this is another tool for adjusting the 3D version
In the case of other 2D tools, these 2D tools are used to make adjustments to the 2D version
So in general, it's going to be used in 3D and 2D windows
So here, because we're running out of time, I'm just going to give you a general overview
So if you want to make a very convenient financial production
Well, actually, at the moment, our cloud software is not a software that specializes in financial management
So we're currently
The support for financial functions is relatively limited
So you can also learn about this
Okay, next
So here's the second question
The second question
You say it
Then let's start with the teacher
Okay, so the second question is to ask whether it is possible to add a simpler function by wearing a日字扣 or T-code
Because our日字扣 or T-code, like this kind of buckle
Its shape
It's actually a thousand faces and then it's not the same size
So it's hard for us to develop a function to make it a unified implementation
So like this kind of buckle, we actually need to master some skills and methods
So we hope you can continue to follow our live broadcast
We will be in the next live broadcast
In addition to one of our real buckle content
A share
So keep following
I'll introduce you to this little trick in the future
Then there's someone in the chat room
Someone said when to add a function
According to the function
Are you talking about the sign outside the clothes?
Can you explain in more detail why you want such a function?
Then let's talk about the next question first
Then I'll take a look at your explanation later
Next
Can you do a similar one in 3D
Is the function of the smart pen
This may be more difficult
Because of the software of 1T
It is a 2D tablet software
Then its software design logic
In fact, it is based on the logic of a 2D tablet software
To be designed
And our clone
When it was first created
It is based on the logic of a 3D software
To carry out functional design
So it's going to match the 1T
It may be more difficult if you are used to it
Because our user background
It includes a board teacher
Then there are also designers
It is also possible that some of them have a 3D technical background
So think about it in a comprehensive way
It may be more difficult to make our 3D
This is this conventional tool
Make a smart pen
It may be more difficult
Because it may be for other people with background
He may not necessarily be used to
Such an operation
Of course, if there is any more in the future
Convenient operation methods
We will also consider communicating with development
See if it is possible to make an optimization
Let's look at the next one
The next one is to ask us
There are many activities
To allow corporate customers to participate
And then we have an official one
Teaching WeChat group
Or allow non-entrepreneurial users to participate
In our offline training activities
About our official one
There is no teaching WeChat group at the moment
Because we are for personal users and corporate users
Is the scope of service is different
And we are currently limited in manpower
Then I hope everyone can understand
But this is but this does not mean
We don't pay attention to our personal users
You can see that we are now this live broadcast
Has also been online
To do these free live broadcast courses
And then on our various social platforms
Xiaoxi also gave everyone to do
A reply to our question
That's all we can give
Some benefits to personal users
In fact, at the same time
You can also pay attention to our official website
There is a forum on it
You can also communicate with users on the forum
Or you can ask some questions on the forum
Then we also have
We will also have a background
To reply to these questions on our official website
Yes
Then the next one
How to import the stage made by the other three software
Into the cloud
And make its lighting and sticker effect unchanged
If you are using other software
The stage created by this stage
You can export it inside
DAE format files
Or OBJ can also
When exporting
If your lighting
Is just a sticker
That is to say, it's just a picture
Then this picture can be normally imported
Into the cloud
But if you are in the other three software
To its lighting
To do some
That is, people in other software
In a three-dimensional environment
Lighting settings
This kind of lighting setting
There is no way to import it
Into the cloud
So it depends on the situation
If it's a sticker
If you import it into the cloud
If it's not normal
You have to check it out
Some of the stickers when you export
Is there a problem with the sticker option
But normally
Stickers can be imported
Lighting parameters do not work
In fact, the rendering engine in cloud
In fact, it also supports
Various types of lighting
That is to say
For its lighting
A self-defined one
Can be operated
Can be designed
Is very strong
So you can import it again
After such a scene
Use this kind of lighting material in cloud
Tool
There are also top lights
Lighting lights
And so on
Various types of lights
You can also
Combine these lights
Is to optimize your lighting environment
A design
Next one
Next question
How to bind the non-system pre-set model
System pre-set model
Showing action
What about this
In 6.0
Is added
An automatic virtual model transfer
Such a function
Then you can
Our non-system pre-set model
Binding on our
A person's Google
After binding Google
We can use our system
Those shows
Posts
You can use it
What about the specific operation
You can go and review our 6.0
The content of the new function live broadcast
That content is also
I will introduce
So you can take a look
I saw someone say in the chat
The official website is often
There is often no connection
Then it seems that the connection is not stable
This is actually
This question we actually have
Occasionally found
So we are now with the development
Is following up on this question
Then next year
There should be an optimization
So if you think
If the official website is not very convenient
Our WeChat background
You can also send messages to our WeChat background
Then we are here
That background
The little c received
Will also give you a reply
Next question
The function of the text editor and the print cloth
What is the difference
Why should it be used separately
In fact
The function of the text editor and the print cloth
Is very similar
Then if there is any difference
Then the text editor is
Is in
Let's take a look at the software
In the fabric here
Let me use a piece of fabric for him
He is here
In the texture setting of the fabric
There is a text editor here
Then here
If you go to make a print cloth
I don't have a picture here
If you made a piece of print cloth
Below
But for this text
You can also do it again
A text setting for his text
In fact, whether it is the text of the cloth
Or the text of the print cloth
It is realized through the text editor
So his function is very similar
So what's the difference
We use the text editor on the text
When doing multiple layer settings
He uses the same material as the text
The same material
Then if you are in the text editor
That is, on the print cloth
If you make another print cloth below
But on the print cloth
You can specify a specific type of material separately
For example, you can do it on your cloth
Some hot gold effects
Hot gold stars and so on
Then that
You can take a look at our 6.0
A description of the new function live broadcast
Have been mentioned above
That is to say
On the new print cloth
You can additionally specify a type of material
This is a difference
The other difference is
We do print on the cloth
He is actually with you
The principle is to be combined
Is a picture
Then if you use the print cloth
He will additionally generate one
Such a material of a drawing
So when you come to
When you are in the color mode
You have a cloth
In addition, you will have a texture picture
That is to say, you will have two materials
In your
This this this this this this material
In the material list
So this is a different point of him
Let's go back to the PPT just now
Let's go back to the PPT
Next one
Next question
Can cloud add camera tracking function?
So far, this function
We don't have it here
Then this piece of function
In fact, it is related to our post-production
Then we recommend
If you want to use this function
You can use some other software
For example, Daz
Then if you say
If you develop this part of the function
Will definitely notify everyone
Next one
Is there an official training system class?
At present, our official training class
Now it's just open to business users
Because we are also currently limited in manpower
For this kind of public class
Training class
In the future, if you say
If you have enough manpower
We will consider arranging
So this is also up to the following
A plan
Next
In fact, if you want to learn cloud classes now
You can directly pass our
Basic training courses on Bilibili
You can learn basic courses first
Then learn our advanced courses in the package
Yes, this series of master car
In fact, basically here
In fact, most of the skills are covered
So
Come in and learn well
You can still learn well
Then let's look at the next question
Next question
How to better integrate models and backgrounds
How to choose a background picture
Has the effect been more realistic
Then how do we choose
Our background picture
In fact, if you look at the special live broadcast of Mr. Yan
He actually has a background picture
A choice
Then he chooses a picture
That is, if we want to choose this picture
It is best to choose one with depth
Is a picture with a transparent relationship
Is to make your model look
Is integrated with the background
Because he has a transparent relationship
For example, if there is a street view
He has a transparent relationship
It seems that people are standing on that street
In this case, this kind of integration
The effect will be better
If you want the effect to be more realistic
In fact, it can also be in our class
To build our one
Scenic stage and so on
In the live broadcast of Tina's show
The last one
It's also about this
If you are interested
You can review the video of that issue
Next
How to adjust the model action
It's the same as the picture action
A very interesting question
You can do this
In your
You can
Draw a very large board in Clue
The size of this board
Can be created according to the height of the model in your 3D window
Then
To put you
There is a picture of such a real person action
Applied on the large board in the way of textual drawing
Then you move that board
To your 3D window
The position of the virtual model
A state of overlapping with your virtual model
Then
Through this overlapping state
According to the posture of the picture action
To adjust your Clue virtual model
One action
Is
It is equivalent to putting a picture
The action of the model above
With the virtual model of Clue
Reunite
Then you go to Clue
The model inside
Let's see
I see some questions in the bulletin board
Let's answer a little bit
I see someone said
What is the use of the backrest U3MA fabric file
How to open and use
U3M
It should be
Another software inside
Use another
It should be
The one of Vizu
The one of the scan machine
The file of such a format
Then U3M
It should be used in the format of another software
Then Vizu
It can be created in such a format
Then U3M
It should be used in the format of another software
Then Vizu
It can be created in such a format
When you create a draft
Pay attention to select the format
Select the XTX format file
Then XTX can be imported to Clue
You can take a look at this
In our software interface
In the material section
Right click
Import or import
Everyone can
Import
Then you can see the backrest here
These three
One is Substance
One is AXF
There is also XTX
Then this is your
The scan machine of the accessory
The format of the scan machine
In this way
Input in
Blocked?
Blocked by U3M
Here
Take a look
One is Substance
One is AXF
One is XTX
What we need is
A file of such a format
It can be exported through Vizu scanning
Again
Right click
Import
Right click on your material
In this format
U3M is not Vizu
Which thing are you producing?
U3M is not a Vizu
Then why is it not Vizu?
Then why is it is not Vizu?
I have not seen Vizu
I have not seen anything
Then why is it not Vizu?
You can see in the dialog box
What is Vizu?
Browse to BrowseWell's fabric format
Ah, use3MA is BrowseWell's fabric format?
Then there's no way to use it in Clover, you can't
You can only use ZFAB in Clover
In other words, fabric files can't be integrated into different systems
Let's go to the next one
This question...
Such a silly question
Can you make your own model's eyelashes longer?
The answer is no
FeiFei's eyelashes are already very long
Aren't they long enough?
The third one is also an interesting question
Can the model in the simulation game be used in Clover?
I don't think so
Clover can be used in the OBJ format
Or in the FDX format
Of course, the model in the simulation game
I don't think it can be used in Clover
I don't think it can be used in the OBJ format
Because after all...
If you have the ability to make it out
Then it can be used
It's OBJ and FDX
Just recognize these two formats
Next one
The front and back colors of the fabric are not the same
In addition to adding hangings and turning the surface
If you don't want to add hangings, is there any other way?
Then we will use this question
This is the second question of the draw
You can brush up the chat
Everyone pay attention
Who knows the answer to this question
You can brush it up
I've been learning for a year
This is a relatively basic question
The front and back colors are not the same
In addition to adding hangings and turning the surface
Is there any other way?
The fastest way
Brush up the chat
Anyone who knows the answer can brush it up
Don't rush
I see some people have written it upside down
Take your time
The prize for this drawing is also
A set of Clou customized humidifiers, fans and lights
Everyone brush it up
I've already seen the correct answer
Then later
Our Hechuan Lu Zhou Juelun will tie it up
We're going to start to tie it up
Everyone brush it up
Brush it up
Anyone who knows the answer, brush it up
Don't copy the answer
Later we will tie it up
It's also according to the order
If the first one is wrong
Then the second one is the winner
Let's take a look
The first one who answers correctly
Then the prize is yours
Brush it up
We're about to tie it up
Everyone brush it up
Almost all of them...
They all know
Okay good
Let's begin to tie it up
We're about to start, we'll count down
Everyone brush it up
We'll start to tie it up
Count down, ready
Three
Two
3, 2, 1, end
Let's take a look
Can we zoom in?
Save it
This one
Two questions
I feel like everyone answered half of the questions
Then I'll take the one with the clearest answer
I'll take the one with the clearest answer
This one?
Wait
Is it her again?
No
It's her
Really?
That's not good
I'm sorry
We also got
Let me see what it is
One more
Let's move on to the next one
Okay
If it's her
Make sure it's her
Yes, it's her
Did you memorize it?
If we don't get it right this time, we'll have to do it again
Everyone didn't get it right
It's so annoying
Yes, it's her
It's very clear
Yes, it's you again
I...
After looking hard at it
I'm very crispy
It's a kind of sushi
Isn't it?
I'm sure
You want to keep going
Again
You want it right now
This is my Photoshoots
It's too big
You don't need to write
One more
I'm already tired
So howusu
You're awake
Our weigh국
How do we weighYou?
1495 is confused
Let's do it again, we're going to draw again
Let's do it again, we're going to draw the second round
Because the first round, we let 1495 draw again, are you guys happy?
The answer is clearer
Okay, let's get ready
Are you ready? Counting down
Time's up!
Let's show it to everyone
If it's still 1495, then it's fine
Set the double-sided pattern
Just this one
Be careful
Yes, this one
Set the double-sided pattern
Yes, set the double-sided pattern
I can understand
Two patterns
It's not very clear, okay?
Okay
Okay, then congratulations to this one
Xiaojing Zui Mei
The ID is Xiaojing Zui Mei
She got the right answer
Let's take a look
Let's cut it
X2
The second one?
Yes
Can you see it?
You, say it again
Xiaojing
Why is it so clear?
Well, first of all, she wrote only 2 patterns
It's not very clear
So we, will move on to our
Xiaojing Zui Mei set double pattern
Well, congratulations to Xiaojing Zui Mei
That's congratulations to the ID of the most beautiful student of Xiaojing
Then, after our live show
You can breathe through Bilibili
We will share it with everyone
You can contact us via our official Wechat account
and send us a private message
and also tell us your address
and a series of other information
We will contact you after the New Year's Eve
and will send you gifts
Then we...
What's wrong?
Next one
After we finish the draw, we still have...
Sorry
We still have one last question
This question
This fan asked a good question
How do you become a CLOU fan?
How many elements?
The first element is of course
the pace with our CLOU livestream
The second one
is that I need to spend more time
to study
some
skills
That is to say, while studying
I need to think more
That's probably it
What do you think?
Let's talk about how to become a CLOU fan
Everyone is so modest
Yes
Today I saw everyone hand in their homework
Everyone is a CLOU fan
Yes
It's not like they want to ask
Actually I think
you are already a CLOU fan
Yes
Okay
If you want to become a CLOU fan
you can follow
our next livestream
and keep learning
There are a few more questions
We suggest
you watch our livestream again
One is
how to do the
Zhu Pian Xiu
You can take a look at
the 8th class of
the master's direct car
There is a detailed explanation
in it
Don't shout, Dingqiu
Someone asked
how to quickly do the
pressure fan effect
It's obvious
You haven't watched the previous one
It's in our winter
It's done by Nico
Someone asked
what to do if the picture
is not clear
You can watch the first class of
the master's direct car
to learn
how to make your
pressure fan effect better
These questions
may be hidden in
a small part of the
live class
You have to watch it carefully
Some of you
have asked
these questions
These questions
such as
whether you can
introduce how to
put the code
and how to
fix the hair
We will try our best
to answer these questions
in 2021
I see
you are asking
if you can share
our basic live
Our materials
have been shared
in WeChat
You can also see
the works we just
introduced
Many of them
are taught by
the master's direct car
You can see
after basic teaching
there is no problem
with the master's work
You can try it
I believe
everyone can do well
How to deal with
a very small amount of
pressure fan effect
How to deal with
a very small amount of
pressure fan effect
I don't know
what kind of pressure fan
you use
You can use
a higher PPI
If you can't do it
you can use
something like
P40 Pro
You can use
a better camera
to film
but when you
film
you can't control
the amount of pressure
You can't control
You can use
scanning
Is this what you asked?
I don't know
what kind of material you
use
If the material you use
includes hair
and transparent channels
because it involves
a lot of light
it might be
influenced
How to go to your
work
You can check
our WeChat public number
You can send us
an invitation
Not only our
invitation
but also some of our
famous clothes
You can get them
from our WeChat public number
You can come to work
Do you know?
I would like to
ask you
if you have
any questions
about your
clothing
or your
You can ask
our WeChat public number
It's
If you want to see the trap, it is recommended that you pull your camera closer and show a partial detail picture to see the trap details.
Because this is similar to the real situation.
When you look at an object from a distance, you can't see it clearly.
You can't see the depth of the trap in the 3D window.
Check the type of trap material in the 3D window.
If it's a thick texture surface, it can't be a texture surface.
The texture surface can't see the thickness.
Is there a lot of companies in Shandong that use clothes?
Yes, there is.
We can look at the next one.
The next one is a mysterious gift I prepared for you.
So you don't know what the next one is.
Xiaoxi will tell you about it.
Looking back at this year's live broadcast, our teachers have worked very hard.
They have spent a lot of time and energy on the live broadcast.
I believe you must have felt that the content of each live broadcast is different.
It is also carefully prepared by the teachers.
Xiaoxi has always been...
interacting with everyone on the Internet and answering everyone's questions.
So I have always received a lot of warm words from everyone.
But in fact, I have never shown it to the teachers.
So this time, in our special live broadcast at the end of the year,
I organized it a little bit.
It's really just a little bit.
I'm really too busy to organize so much content.
I want to give it as a small gift to our live broadcast designers.
So next, let's take a look at the fans' hearts.
You can also find your comments in the comments.
Maybe there are.
Can you see it?
Let me take a look.
I think I can.
Wow.
Excuse me.
I can't hear what your teachers are saying.
I am already...
The little dog is going to the end of the broadcast.
这位同学真的很幼稚 This classmate is really very childish.
哇,第十一个投稿! Wow, the eleventh one!
之前我们微信公众号的作品展示的部分呢,之前我们微信公众号的作品展示的部分呢
我们一直都是有收到大家的投稿的,相信大家如果关注我们的公众号,也会看到每一期的下面都会有
国内的粉丝投稿的佳作,嗯,哇,可以的,嗯.
那这个呢,就是刚刚我们的reaction部分,我们的Tatika同学给我们的来信。
她也在,她也在,我看到她了。
你看到她了吗?
对,我前面看到Tatika了。
是吗?
是的。
她真的写得特别特别感人,我那天看到她的那个来信的时候,一早看到的。
一早看到的。
一早眼泪就流下来了。
真的希望我们就是说有很多粉丝,有跟我们这位Tatika同学一样,有这样的心声的话。
真的是我们手速惊人的Moi老师,跟语速惊人的Abby老师。
那还有一部分呢。
我真的。
哎哟,哎哟,哎哟,丽丽娅老师不要哭了。
丽丽娅老师都哭了。
看到大家,其实看到这一次大家教的那个reaction的作业,真的是可以感受到,我们这一年的直播工作,真的是没有白费,不管是前期的准备还是晚上的加班。
是能看得出来,就是给大家带来的这种切实的这种帮助。
嗯。
哎,不要哭了。
不要哭了。
我就很容易感动。
那这里呢,是我们bilibili上面一小部分粉丝。
哦,不对,这边是,说错了。
这边是bilibili的,这边是微信的,我只能整理这么多了,不然也装不下,今天晚上都放不完了。
一小部分粉丝对我们比较有爱的评论。
哇,谢谢弹幕。
哇,谢谢,谢谢大家。
哇,谢谢弹幕里面大家的评论。
这个是真的有点看不清楚了。
太多了。
是吧,太多了,实在是太多了。
那大家也可以看到像前面的第三个部分呢,对于今年直播的遗留问题,我们也都进行了解答。
那么我们2020年的直播到此就要结束了。
到此就要和大家告一个段落了。
那我们就大家在先前直播里面给我们弹幕里面提出的意见,我们都有在后期制作过整理的,做了总结。
那么大家可以看一下,接下来这是我们目前要确定的明年的直播主题的预告。
大家可以从伤感的氛围里面走出来。
大家可以看一下,这是我们明年的直播计划,现在是可以确定的有这三个部分。
大家可以看一下,有没有你中意的呢?
包括前面问的那个群称,就是礼服的群称怎么制作的,我们在婚纱专题到时候也会安排上哦。
哇,都中意,谢谢,谢谢,谢谢。
太好了,太好了。
谢谢。
哇。
那像大家看了之前的评论呢。
谢谢。
其实有的时候,偶尔小C也会遇到一些不太友好的评论。
那希望大家可以善待一下小C。
如果有的时候呢,我们没有及时回复你,也请不要着急和失落。
因为也是我一个人在进行这所有问题的回答嘛。
然后杰伦也会帮我做一些技术方面的解答。
所以像每天我们。
像每天我们的那个后台都会说。
收到十几,十几条,有的时候会有99家的那个消息。
所以可能我一时回不过来,大家也不要太着急或者失落。
只要大家是从通过官方渠道来问我们的呢,我都会一一去看去回答的。
那最后呢,小C觉得我们老师们辛辛苦苦做了一年的直播。
希望大家能够在弹幕里面告诉一下对于我们直播的感想和反馈。
以及未来,大家听清楚了。
以及是未来你们想要看到什么类型的Cloud直播都要告诉我们。
好吗?
那现在弹幕大家可以刷一波刷起来,告诉我们你们明年2021年还想看到什么主题的直播教学呢?
那么我们也会在明年的直播计划里面给大家考虑,更大的去优化我们的Cloud直播。
那弹幕可以刷一波刷起来,这是我们今天的最后一波出讲了。
想。
明年想看什么题材的教学直播。
刷起来,弹幕刷起来。
弹幕刷起来,弹幕刷起来。
接下来要出讲了。
明年想要看到直播内容,或者说是对于我们的一些建议啊,都可以。
没事嘟嘟脸就好了,今天已经看过固了。
大家可以想要学什么尽管说啊,今天是一个许愿环节。
对,今天是许愿。
等一下就是我们的那个周久仁要开始。
哈哈哈哈。
给大家截屏了啊。
哇,开始刷了已经。
机器人类,天哪。
机器人类。
机器人类是燕做的那个。
伴郎老师做的。
伴郎老师。
男装。
布料属性,牛仔真实。
包包。
包包之前有做过。
对。
如果说之前的包包没有满足你的需求,你想要学别的包的话,你可以详细说一下。
对,详细说明是什么类型的包包。
对。
刷起来刷起来。
今天大许愿许完愿还能抽奖。
是不是很划算。
时装大篇渲染示范。
泳衣专题。
盔甲。
哇塞,盔甲可以去跟刚刚那位Loyal Studio使一下心。
哈哈哈哈。
时尚大篇也可以跟Loyal Studio取奖金。
时尚大篇也可以去问Loyal Studio取奖金。
我们要不开始抽吧。
开始抽吧。
大家准备刷起来了,我们要开始抽了。
杰伦要准备起来,杰伦这次手速要快一点。
杰伦手速准备好了吗?
好,准备。
准备啊,预备。
结皮。
好多啊。
感觉你服是婚纱汉服的好多啊。
哇哇哇。
感觉明年日程又可以安排满了。
哈哈哈哈。
阿。
那恭喜刚刚害我们Lydia老师哭出来的。
哈哈哈哈。
杰伦给大家看一下。
嗯。
哦。
Oh, sorry.
Thank you.
Tatika, don't forget to contact our official account.
We will also send you gifts in Yunnan.
Remember to tell us your address and how to contact us.
Ah, the comments are congratulating her. Congratulations.
Congratulations.
Our tears didn't flow in vain.
Our audience is so loving.
Thank you.
Lastly,
we would like to
We are nearing the end of our live stream.
We would like to introduce
a vlog about the daily life of our designer, Chloe.
We recorded it last month.
We would like to use this vlog
as the end of our live stream.
I hope you guys can
understand us better through this vlog.
Thank you for watching our video.
Please don't forget to
Like and Subscribe us.
See you next time.
Bye-bye.
Bye. Bye.
This is a true love story song
A triumph in the glory song
With only one small caveat
This one hasn't happened yet
It's not the strongest narrative
But details aren't imperative
For panders it's the way it ends
And they've got sixteen mutual friends
This is the animal spirit
And it's the heartfelt lyrics
Put them together, you can hear it all
So if anyone knows
This is the animal spirit
And it's the heartfelt lyrics
Put them together, you can hear it all
When a star really grows
Now everyone seems unaware
That these two are a destined pair
But I checked out their astral chart
And this one ends somewhere good
And I know she reads astrology
And he can't stand astrology
But he's quick with an apology
When he wisecracks the zodiac system
Am I fair?
This is Zhou Xianwen
Put them together, you can hear it all
So dear you as well
This is the animal spirit
And it's the heartfelt lyrics
Ugh delicious
Don't treat my child over
Put them together, you can hear it all
So get this one ugly
This is the animal spirit
And it's the heartfelt lyrics
For panders it can't end
Bugün kendal
This is Xiongけて
Xiong mujiz
Karli
Xiongtlan
אנחנו
Thank you for watching. Please subscribe to our channel if you like our videos.
This is the end of our year-end special live broadcast.
I hope everyone will be healthy and happy in the coming new year.
Of course, you can also learn more about our CLO software during the holiday season.
You really want to go to work, right?
Let's practice more CLO software for the next three days.
Practice well and give us a reward.
We look forward to seeing you again.
In the end, let's all...
Jielun, come here.
In the end...
In the end, let's all...
Jielun is here too.
In the end, let's all wish everyone...
Happy New Year!
Bye bye.
See you tomorrow.
Thank you everyone.
Bye bye.
Bye bye. See you next year.